[{"answer": "When I came here in -- in Wild Card, we just came here for just a vacation and looking for a boxing gym for workout.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 48, "question": "What happens when you come that day?", "qSentId": 47}, {"answer": "I never expected what I have done in boxing and, you know, it's -- it's amazing and unbelievable.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 56, "question": "Can you believe what's happened to you in your career?", "qSentId": 55}, {"answer": "It's -- there's a pressure, you know, because all Filipinos, millions of Filipinos, they're hoping for victory in the fight.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 67, "question": "How do you feel?", "qSentId": 66}, {"answer": "How I feel -- of course, I feel happy and people believing my talent, my capability in boxing.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 73, "question": "How do you feel when people say you're the best fighter there's ever been?", "qSentId": 72}, {"answer": "I think this is -- this is part of the -- of the -- my career.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 91, "question": "How do you manage to try and kill people with your hands but not hate?", "qSentId": 90}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 102, "question": "What did you hope to achieve when you were doing those fights?", "qSentId": 101}, {"answer": "The --", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 107, "question": "Did you nearly give up then?", "qSentId": 106}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 109, "question": "Did you think about giving up then?", "qSentId": 108}, {"answer": "I'm excited and, you know, I've been training eight weeks for this fight.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 113, "question": "When you get in the ring for a fight like you are tomorrow, as you walk in, how do you really feel?", "qSentId": 112}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, you know, it's my experience, before a fight, with short hair, I feel like I'm weak.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 119, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 118}, {"answer": "Being a public servant, this is a serious job, not like a boxer, you're entertaining people.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 125, "question": "How realistic is this for you?", "qSentId": 124}, {"answer": "That's what I am trying to do, to change the -- you know, the politics in the Philippines.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 131, "question": "Would you like to be in a position of power to change that, to make it a more honest politics?", "qSentId": 130}, {"answer": "Making money -- I'm happy, because, of course, every fight I make millions of dollars.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 138, "question": "Does it motivate you, money?", "qSentId": 137}, {"answer": "I never, you know -- right now, I'm not thinking about that.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 142, "question": "What do you honestly think?", "qSentId": 141}, {"answer": "Like what I said, I'm more -- you know, I always fight whatever my promoter is giving to me, the opponent.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 144, "question": "Would you like to?", "qSentId": 143}, {"answer": "It's hard to say.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 148, "question": "Do you think you'd beat him?", "qSentId": 147}, {"answer": "I believe so.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 166, "question": "What brought you two together -- fate?", "qSentId": 165}, {"answer": "Yes, you can.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 190, "question": "Can you tell by a fighter's eyes?", "qSentId": 189}, {"answer": "He's like a son to me.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 200, "question": "What makes Manny special to you?", "qSentId": 199}, {"answer": "Yes, I get at least about 30 a day that come to the door in --", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 210, "question": "And how many Filipinos come and see him?", "qSentId": 209}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 212, "question": "Every day in Los Angeles?", "qSentId": 211}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 216, "question": "I mean, is it as crazy as it sounds when he goes back?", "qSentId": 215}, {"answer": "Important in life is you know how to -- to love people and to be friendly to everybody.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 225, "question": "Apart from God and -- and your worship of God, what are the other things that you think are important in life?", "qSentId": 224}, {"answer": "It's hurt me, but, you know, people don't believe him.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 239, "question": "That's got to hurt you, right?", "qSentId": 238}, {"answer": "-- the focus --", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 243, "question": "And you really want to beat him, don't you?", "qSentId": 242}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 245, "question": "I mean more than -- more than most fights?", "qSentId": 244}, {"answer": "Yes, we have the right stuff to beat Mayweather.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 253, "question": "Would he beat Floyd Mayweather?", "qSentId": 252}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 259, "question": "And is -- and is the trump card with Manny that you've -- you've developed now, almost equal power with both hands?", "qSentId": 258}, {"answer": "It's -- it's not only for myself, but, you know, I keep fighting because I want to know I'm happy to give -- giving honor to my country.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 268, "question": "Why do men want to do this to each other?", "qSentId": 267}, {"answer": "You know, we warm up a little bit and go through the routines and when you make this move, you know, what move he is going to make.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 273, "question": "What do you say to a guy like Manny, who has won everything?", "qSentId": 272}, {"answer": "Always.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 280, "question": "Do you pray before a fight?", "qSentId": 279}, {"answer": "After -- after the fight.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 284, "question": "Well, you are a singer, right?", "qSentId": 283}, {"answer": "After.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 287, "question": "So you pray before and you sing after?", "qSentId": 286}, {"answer": "Because he fights the way people want to see fighters fight, and because his genuine goodness shines through.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 310, "question": "Bob, what makes this guy television promotional gold dust?", "qSentId": 309}, {"answer": "Sometimes.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 323, "question": "Is that true -- is that true, Manny?", "qSentId": 322}, {"answer": "Because I -- I feel it in my heart.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 327, "question": "-- why -- why do you do that?", "qSentId": 326}, {"answer": "Yes, all of them.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 329, "question": "You feel sorry for them?", "qSentId": 328}, {"answer": "Yes, I'm just doing my job.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 332, "question": "Even when you're pummeling them?", "qSentId": 331}, {"answer": "It's --", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 334, "question": "What's it -- what's it like being hit hard by somebody very, very good?", "qSentId": 333}, {"answer": "Because if you don't hit hard, your opponent hits you hard.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 338, "question": "I mean, I -- I can imagine, but you know?", "qSentId": 337}, {"answer": "ACQUIAO: You can feel it, but if you -- like if you get hit a good one, you can feel it.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 347, "question": "Do you feel it in the actual moment?", "qSentId": 346}, {"answer": "Manny is very accurate.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 354, "question": "Does he ever miss and whack you one?", "qSentId": 353}, {"answer": "The worst punch I guess was Tyson.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 358, "question": "Of all the boxers, what's been the worst punch you ever had to take?", "qSentId": 357}, {"answer": "Well, there was a period of time where Ali was absolutely super, when he became champion and before the draft.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 373, "question": "Where does Manny rank, genuinely, do you think, in the 46 years you've been in the fight game?", "qSentId": 372}, {"answer": "If I could make that fight happen, then the government, U.S. government might send me over to bring about peace in the Mideast, because I've got a guy in Mayweather who won't fight Manny Pacquiao because no matter what the money is, he knows he will get knocked out.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 377, "question": "How much money could you make from promoting the Pacquiao/Mayweather fight if it ever happened?", "qSentId": 376}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 384, "question": "Do you agree with that, Freddie?", "qSentId": 383}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 404, "question": "Do you respect him or not?", "qSentId": 403}, {"answer": "Everybody I respect.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 408, "question": "Everybody?", "qSentId": 407}, {"answer": "You know, America is -- for me, it's the best country.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 436, "question": "Why do you say that?", "qSentId": 435}, {"answer": "The freedom, all the people, you know, and also the Constitution of America.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 439, "question": "Why do you think that?", "qSentId": 438}, {"answer": "ACQUIAO: Well, I'm -- I'm looking for -- I -- I'm thinking for that -- not to get hurt.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 451, "question": "Do you worry that you may fight just too long and suffer irreparable damage?", "qSentId": 450}, {"answer": "Well, Manny had me over.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 464, "question": "Are you going to be helping him promote his campaign?", "qSentId": 463}, {"answer": "Well, I'll be -- it keeps me going because in 2022, I'll be 91 years of age, I'll come in on my cane.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 472, "question": "So this could be for both of you the last big hurrah?", "qSentId": 471}, {"answer": "Not yet.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 476, "question": "Have you worked out your cabinet position yet?", "qSentId": 475}, {"answer": "The tremors go away and the shaking and it's just like --", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 525, "question": "When he goes in the ring and he does the mitts, it goes away, right, Freddie?", "qSentId": 524}, {"answer": "I'm not sure.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 528, "question": "Why do you think that is?", "qSentId": 527}, {"answer": "I had like a 41-13 record at the end.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 541, "question": "Was that your record?", "qSentId": 540}, {"answer": "I'm a trauma study.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 544, "question": "Did you think the condition you have now is down to boxing or not?", "qSentId": 543}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 550, "question": "Do you assume the same about Muhammed Ali?", "qSentId": 549}, {"answer": "RUM: And his promoter.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 559, "question": "How do you feel having been his friend for so long?", "qSentId": 558}, {"answer": "These tattoos, it's is a meteor.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 569, "question": "How many do you have?", "qSentId": 568}, {"answer": "This is old, when I was young.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 576, "question": "And that one?", "qSentId": 575}, {"answer": "It is a rose with a snake.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 578, "question": "Does it mean anything or no?", "qSentId": 577}, {"answer": "It is a green snake.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 581, "question": "What does that mean?", "qSentId": 580}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 583, "question": "Does it have a meaning?", "qSentId": 582}, {"answer": "There is a rose bud and a snake.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 588, "question": "It means you want to hit people, right?", "qSentId": 587}, {"answer": "Jimuel, his name is Emanuel Junior.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 593, "question": "What are your children's full names?", "qSentId": 592}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 601, "question": "You named your daughter after my queen?", "qSentId": 600}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 607, "question": "Have you met the queen?", "qSentId": 606}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 611, "question": "Do you like the royal family?", "qSentId": 610}, {"answer": "I like them, you know.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 613, "question": "Why do you like them?", "qSentId": 612}, {"answer": "My dream is to help people.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 626, "question": "But what else do you think about?", "qSentId": 625}, {"answer": "A little bit.", "docId": "111111pmt", "aSentId": 667, "question": "Was that -- that was -- was it bigger than Tyson's?", "qSentId": 666}]